efreedom.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy - eFreedom

**Your Privacy Is Important to Us**  
eFreedom LLC (“eFreedom,” “We,” “Our,” or “Us”) values the privacy of the visitors to its website (“Website) and the Users of the services provided thereon (individually, “User” or “you,” and collectively, “Users”), and makes it a priority to protect any personally identifiable information it obtains from its users. This Privacy Policy explains eFreedom’s collection, use, and protection of your personal information on and in connection with the website and all content, services and/or products provided through the website (collectively, the “Services”). If you have any questions that this policy does not address, please contact us [legal@efreedom.com](mailto:legal@efreedom.com).

By accessing the Services, registering as a User, using our Service or by otherwise submitting your personal information to us through an event registration, you give your consent to the collection and use of personal information as explained in this policy. The term “personal information” refers to non-public information that personally relates to or identifies you (such as your name, password, age, gender, email address, postal mailing address, zip code, home/mobile telephone number, investment objectives, investment experience, assets and income, and other similar information). Non-personally identifiable information collected on the website may include, without limitation, website pages viewed; video, webinar, archived presentations viewed; sites visited before visiting the Site; frequency of visits; clickstream data; browser type; operating system; organization name; articles and special reports; books; internet connection speed; time spent viewing pages of our website or using certain features of our website; demographic data such as server locations; clickstream data; location services; server location, cookies existing on your computer; search criteria used and results; date and time of access or visits to our website; frequency of visits to our website; connection speed, and other information which does not specifically identify you.

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. YOUR CONSENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY CREATES LEGAL OBLIGATIONS FOR YOU AND FOR US. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR WEBSITE.**

By using the website and/or Services, you accept the practices and terms set forth in our Privacy Policy as it may be updated from time to time in eFreedom’s sole and absolute discretion.

**How We Collect Information**  
When you register for an event or an account for a membership or any eFreedom Services we collect certain personal information from you to open an account, transact business, communicate with you, verify your identity, and fulfill legal and regulatory requirements. We call this your “Profile.” If you choose to provide such information, during registration or otherwise, you give eFreedom the permission to use and store it consistent with this Privacy Policy. We may also obtain your personal information from your transactions with us or other users through the Services, or from third parties such as accreditation verification service providers. If we combine or associate information from other sources with personal information that you provide directly to us through or in connection with the Services, we will treat the combined information as personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

When you visit the website, whether or not you register for an account, we may send one or more cookies. Cookies make it easier for you to navigate our Website by, among other things, “remembering” your identity so that you do not have to input your password multiple times as you navigate between webpages on the website and/or as you access the Services. This use of cookies for authentication (i.e., verifying that you are who you say you are) is an essential component of site security. “Server logs” can be either a single log file or several log files automatically created and maintained by a server of activity performed by the server, which can include information about any transaction you conduct with the server. Please note that if you decline to use cookies, you may experience reduced functionality or slower site response times. Declining to use our authentication-related cookies may prevent you from using the Website altogether. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the website's features.

**Technology**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are issued to your computer when you visit a website and that store and sometimes track information about your use of the Services. eFreedom uses cookies to help recognize you as a repeat visitor, to improve the quality of our Services, and to try and make your browsing experience meaningful. When you enter our website, our web server sends a cookie to your computer, which allows us to recognize your computer, but not specifically who is using it. By associating the identification numbers in the cookies with other customer information when, for example, your login to the website or Services, we know that the cookie information relates to you. Some of the cookies used by our Services are served by us, and some are served by third parties who are delivering services on our behalf. The use of cookies by any third parties, including our affiliates or service providers, is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

As you browse eFreedom and its event content pages, our online ad networks may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you. If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, email [legal@efreedom.com](mailto:legal@efreedom.com)  to opt out of these tailored investment opportunities put in place for users. Opting out will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.

**Information We Collect**  
eFreedom collects personal information from you when you visit the website. The majority of information is collected during the registration and/or application process and, while some items are optional, most are required for legal or security purposes. You may choose to provide additional information during subsequent visits to the website, but keep in mind that some of this information will be required if you wish to partake in the Services.

In general, the type of information we collect includes, but is not limited to:

Personal data necessary to assess your eligibility to utilize the Services on the eFreedom platform; and

On-identifiable and aggregated personal data pertaining to your website visits that help us maintain the appropriate features, functionality, and User experience.

**Personal Data**  
Student registration and applications will require you to provide basic personal data. Such information typically includes your name, email address, home address and phone number. 

eFreedom uses this data to:

Identify you when you sign-in to your account;

Enable us to provide you with the Services;

Send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us;

Present projects or opportunities to you when you use the Services which we believe will be of interest based on your geographic location and previous use of the Services;

Determine your credibility to partake in eCommerce opportunities;

Verify that you are at least 18 years of age;

Guard against potential fraud;

Administer your account with us;

Enable us to contact you regarding any question you make through the Services;

Analyze the use of the Services and the people visiting to improve our content and Services;

Use for other purposes that we may disclose to you when we request your information.

Also, if you provide personal information in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your personal information to provide you with access to such Services and to monitor your use of such Services. We also may obtain information about you from third-party sources to verify your identity, so we can properly process your requests and prevent fraud.

eFreedom will also gather the names and email addresses of Users who contact us through the website with questions about our company and/or the “raising capital” platform. We collect this information for the sole purpose of responding to such inquiries and do not store the contact information unless requested to do so, as in the case of job applicants who submit resumes.

**Social Media Features and Benefits**  
Services like Facebook give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network. Our website also includes social media features such as the Facebook Like button, Twitter, and share buttons. These features are interactive mini-programs and may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

**Email Policy**  
eFreedom values the privacy of the users of the services provided thereon and makes it a priority to protect any personal information. Regarding email contact with and from eFreedom, please keep in mind the following: (i) we will send you email relating to your personal profile but will keep these emails to a minimum; (ii) we may send you service-related industry announcements, special interest promotions, featured investments, and other eFreedom news on rare occasions when it is necessary or proper to do so; (iii) you will receive certain email notifications (forwarded messages, notifications, etc.) for which you may opt-out; and (iv) if you email us directly, we may email you back and keep records of all correspondence. It is your responsibility to ensure that you maintain a current email address with eFreedom and notify us if there are any changes.

eFreedom will send you email notifications from time to time. Some notifications are required elements of your educations, services, software and transactions on our platform, such as confirmations of particular actions you have taken. These mandatory notices are sent typically to notify you of a change in status. For example, you will receive a notice when you are confirmed as a new eFreedom student.

Use of any personal information shared in connection therewith is strictly limited to the performance of the task we request and for no other purpose. In the event you indicate an interest in making an investment in educations, services or the purchase of software through our website, we will notify only your coach or customer service representative of your interest and will provide your personal information so that you may be contacted further, and all your questions answered.

We may make certain automatically collected information about your interactions and activities on the Services, such as the business or investment areas of interest to you or you have invested in, and your past activities, projects or proposals, are publicly available on or through the Services. Any such publicly available information will be accessible by other users.

We also send out notices that are required for legal or security purposes. These notifications are sent for your own protection and education on industry standards changes and it is our standard operating procedure to inform you. We also ensure that another person cannot make a change to your account without your knowledge. In other cases, these notifications involve changes to various legal agreements or website policies. These communications are at the discretion of eFreedom. We may also send you responses to emails you send us, if appropriate. We will also send quarterly User surveys requesting User feedback regarding User experience and website operations, or marketing offers from us or from us on behalf of our trainers and affiliates. Completing these surveys, answering requests for feedback, or accepting any offer is strictly voluntary. If you do not wish to receive these surveys, User feedback emails, and/or investment information, please opt out in any offer email you receive from us. Generally, you may not opt out of such Service-related emails.

eFreedom also works with providers of hosting services for the website, electronic signature providers, accreditation verification service providers, and electronic payment service providers. We may engage third parties to help us carry out certain other internal functions such as account processing, client services, or other data collection relevant to our business.

We may disclose your personal information when such disclosure is required or appropriate pursuant to laws, court orders, or securities regulations, including responding to court orders and subpoenas, cooperating with government agencies, other regulatory bodies and law enforcement officials, performing background checks, resolving disputes or performing risk-management functions.

We further reserve the right to disclose any of your personal information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the website or our services, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of eFreedom, its users or others.

In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, personal information may be part of the transferred assets and you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Security Policy and the Website Access Limitations**  
We limit access to the personal information we have about you to those employees who have a legitimate business need to access such information. In keeping with industry standards and practices, we maintain appropriate electronic, physical, and procedural safeguards and controls to protect your information. The website is built upon a secure infrastructure with multiple layers of protection, and we use industry-standard encryption technologies to safeguard your information.

Users are required to identify and authenticate themselves prior to accessing restricted portions of the Services. Generally, identification and authentication take place through the use of your User name and a password and/or while logging in with one of our technical support staff. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential.

The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure, and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security of information sent to us electronically. If we learn of a security systems breach, we may attempt to (i) notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps, (ii) deliver this notice by mail if we feel the means is most efficient under the circumstances; and/or (iii) use commercially reasonable efforts to accomplish these steps and effect this notice in a timely manner, like outbound phone calls or a dialer. To the extent applicable law requires steps in addition to those specified above, we would under all circumstances comply with applicable law.

We may also post a notice on or through the website and the Services in the event of a security breach. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

We have security standards and procedures in place designed to prevent unauthorized access to your accounts and personal information. A key part of this process helps ensure that all information we have about you is accurate and up-to-date. If you ever discover inaccuracies in our data or if your personal information changes, notify [legal@efreedom.com](mailto:legal@efreedom.com) immediately. 

**Applicable Law and Jurisdiction**  
The Website is maintained in the United States of America. By accessing the eFreedom Website, you consent to and authorize the export of personally identifiable information to the United States of America and its storage and use as specified in this Privacy Notice.

This Privacy Notice shall be governed by, construed, and entered in accordance with the laws of the facilities within Florida applicable to contracts deemed to be made within such state, without regard to choose of law or conflict of law provisions thereof. All disputes with respect to this Privacy Notice shall be brought and heard in the Florida State Courts located in Orange County, Orlando, FL. You consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such courts. YOU HEREBY WAIVE YOUR RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY WITH RESPECT TO ANY CLAIM, ACTION, OR PROCEEDING, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, ARISING OUT OF, OR RELATING TO, THIS AGREEMENT TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

**Ongoing Commitment to Your Privacy**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of our former Users as well as our current users. If you choose to become an inactive user, you will continue to be protected by the policies and principles described in this Privacy Policy for as long as your personal information is retained by us. Should you close your account with us, we will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to comply with any applicable legal or regulatory requirements.

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your choices with regards to our collection and use of your user Information or any other aspect of the website or Services, please feel free to contact us by email at [legal@efreedom.com](mailto:legal@efreedom.com).
